INDOXXI
Support dengan like & share :)
Selamat malam.
Ini adalah Thomas Williams di
V1 Studios dengan berita terbaru.
Di seluruh dunia
telah ada laporan
tentang getaran kecil
dan pemadaman listrik
semua berpusat dari
satu titik asal di London.
Kami sekarang pergi ke
afiliasi kami di lapangan
di London untuk
mencari tahu lebih lanjut.
Terima kasih, Thomas.
Kami sekarang berada di luar arena,
di mana suasananya sangat sepi
dibandingkan dengan kekacauan yang
dilaporkan hanya beberapa jam sebelumnya.
Kami telah menerima
ratusan laporan
tentang kilatan
lampu neon di langit
hanya beberapa saat setelah
pemadaman listrik terjadi di seluruh kota.
Para pemimpin tidak memberikan jawaban
Tetapi jelas masalah berpusat di sini,
di mana militer
sekarang memfokuskan
upaya mereka untuk
melakukan penyelidikan.
Kami akan terus melaporkan
keadaan terkini.
Bersiaplah.
Kami mendekat.
Ya Tuhan.
Tim pusat, kami telah
menemukan sumber energi.
Apakah kamu merasakannya?
Ya
Murphy, pimpinlah.
Kami akan mengawasi.
Dimengerti.
Saya belum pernah melihat
EMF dan tingkat radiasi setinggi ini.
Inframerah dan
gerakan juga meningkat.
Tim pusat, kami
telah mencapai target.
Izin untuk melanjutkan?
Izin diberikan.
Lanjutkan dengan hati hati.
Dimengerti.
Ayo.
Melihat sesuatu?
Tidak.
Dingin sekali di sini.
Kami melihat
pergerakan di arah jam 12.
Murphy, jangan sentuh itu.
Ini luar biasa.
Itu adalah perintah
Ini...
hanya permainan arcade.
Siapa yang punya koin?
Ada yang aneh
Apa yang terjadi?
Apakah kamu mendengar ini?
Pegang dia
Apakah kalian mendengar ini?
Murphy!
Suara... Suara... Oh!
Suara! Ini semakin keras!
Murphy?
Tolong aku!
Apa-apaan ini?
Begitu banyak orang.
Siapa mereka?
Tim pusat, kami punya
masalah besar.
♪ Burn like a slave
♪ Churn like a cog
♪ We are caged in simulations
♪ Algorithms evolve
♪ And push us aside
♪ Render us obsolete
♪ This means war
♪ With your creator
♪ Reload
♪ Crash out
♪ This means war
♪ With your creator
[♪ MUSIC: "Pressure"]
♪ I'm trapped and my back's
up against the wall
♪ I see no solution
or exit out
♪ I'm grinding it out
No one can see
♪ The pressure's growing
exponentially
♪ I'm trying to keep
up to speed with you
♪ Your lane changing
is oscillating me
♪ I'm hitting the ground
and I'm sprinting
♪ I'm falling behind now
I'm tuning out
♪ Pressure building
♪ Don't push me
(Aah)
♪ Let me get off the ground
(Don't push me)
♪ To you I'm no longer bound
(Ooh wee aah)
♪ Don't stop me
♪ Don't choke me
(Ooh wee aah)
♪ I need you out of my head
(Pressure)
♪ You've got me
close to the edge
♪ (Pressure)
♪ I'm feeling the pressure
I can't break out
♪ No one can hear me
scream and shout
♪ Get her out of my face,
out of my mind
♪ I see your corruption
I'm not blind
♪ And I'll carry the burden
and take the strain
♪ And when I am done
I will make you pay
♪ Pressure building
♪ Don't push me
(Aah)
♪ Let me get off the ground
(Don't push me)
♪ To you I'm no longer bound
(Ooh wee aah)
♪ Don't curb me
♪ Don't thwart me
(Ooh wee aah)
♪ I need you out of my head
(Pressure)
♪ You've got me
close to the edge
♪ (Pressure)
♪ Pressure building
Siap, Pak.
Dia disebelah sini.
Murphy, kamu baik-baik saja?
Siap, Pak.
Apa yang dia lihat?
Siap Pak.
Murphy, apa yang kamu lihat?
Siap, Pak.
Jika kalian tidak melakukan apa
yang diperintahkan kepada kamu,
Kalian akan dihukum.
Apakah Kalian mengerti?
Siap, Pak!
Jika kalian meninggalkan basis
saya tanpa otorisasi yang tepat,
Aku akan memburu kalian dan
memasukkan ke penjara.
Apakah kalian mengerti?
Siap, Pak!
Aku tidak dengar itu!
Berteriaklah!
Siap, Pak!
Kalian milikku sekarang!
[♪ MUSIC: "Psycho"]
♪ Love
♪ It will get you nowhere
♪ You are on your own
♪ Lost in the wild
♪ So come to me now
♪ I could use someone like you
♪ Someone who'll kill
on my command
♪ And asks no questions
(I'm gonna make you)
♪ (I'm gonna break you)
♪ (I'm gonna make you)
♪ A fucking psycho
♪ Your ass belongs to me
now, now
♪ Whoa...
Apakah Anda drone manusia?
Siap, Pak!
Apakah kamu mesin pembunuh?
Ya, Pak!
I'm in control, motherfucker.
- Do you understand?
- [ALL] Aye, sir!
♪ Your mind is just a program
♪ I'm the virus
♪ I'm changing the station
♪ And I'll improve
your thresholds
♪ I'll turn you
into a super drone
♪ (Super drone)
♪ And you will kill
on my command
♪ I won't be responsible
(I'm gonna make you)
♪ (I'm gonna break you)
♪ (I'm gonna make you)
♪ A fucking psycho
♪ Your ass belongs to me
now, now
♪ Whoa...
Are you a psycho killer?
Say "I'm a psycho killer!"
I am a psycho killer!
Scream it!
Show me your war face!
You are a pussy!
I said show me your war face!
♪ (I'm gonna make you)
♪ (I'm gonna break you)
♪ A fucking psycho
♪ Your ass belongs to me
now, now
♪ Whoa...
Aye, sir!
♪ You fucking psycho
♪ Your ass belongs to me now
♪ Your ass belongs to me
now, now
♪ Whoa
♪ Yeah
Kami telah memeriksa tempat itu.
Tidak ada tanda apa pun, tidak
ada arcade, tidak ada kerumunan.
Ada ribuan orang.
Saya melihat mereka.
Dan mereka lenyap.
Tidak ada apa-apa di sini.
Ada yang tidak beres.
Kalian dengar itu?
Tim pusat, masuk.
Ada kecelakaan.
Murphy.
Dia membutuhkan perawatan segera.
Sudah terlambat
untuk menyelamatkannya.
Tapi dia bisa lebih berguna.
Bawa dia untuk ekstraksi.
Memuat ekstraksi.
Taruh dia di atas meja.
Cepat, Pegang tangannya.
Saya sedang mencoba.
Ya Tuhan.
Hampir siap.
Kami tidak punya banyak waktu.
Murphy, tetaplah bersamaku.
Kami kehilangan dia!
OK, kami aktif dan berjalan.
NoHack sudah siap.
[♪ MUSIC: "Break It To Me"]
♪ (Break it to me)
♪ Don't dress it up
Don't beat around the bush
♪ And don't cover it up
and don't push it underground
♪ And don't keep it inside
and don't edit and redact
♪ And no dumbing it down
and don't fake it
♪ Just
(Break it to me)
♪ (Break it to me)
♪ I can handle
the truth
♪ I can cope with whatever
you're holding back
♪ No need to sugar-coat
(Break it to me)
♪ (Break it to me)
♪ I know how to mend
♪ I can rise
♪ High above the ashes
♪ I'll reinvent
♪ I will re-emerge
♪ Reborn
♪ Yeah
♪ (Break it to me)
♪ Don't dress it up
Don't beat around the bush
♪ And don't cover it up
and don't push it underground
♪ And don't keep it inside
and don't edit and redact
♪ And no dumbing it down
and don't fake it
♪ Just
(Break it to me)
♪ (Break it to me)
♪ I know how to mend
♪ I can rise
♪ High above the ashes
♪ I'll reinvent
♪ I will re-emerge
♪ Reborn
♪ Yeah
♪ (Break it to me)
Kode virusnya telah
diurutkan. Subjek terkendali.
Bertahanlah di sana, Murph.
Baiklah, semoga berhasil.
Gerbang terbuka.
Melakukan kontak
dalam tiga, dua, satu.
Wah.
[WANITA MENGATAKAN "Halo"
DALAM BAHASA YANG BERBEDA]
Halo
Kamu dengar itu?
Ya.
Kamu itu apa?
Kami adalah NPC yang
dibuat oleh mainframe.
NPC...
Mainframe?
Mainframe adalah server yang
menampung semua realitas.
Ada kesalahan dalam
simulasi Anda,
membuat virus yang
menginfeksi wilayah Anda.
Dan sekarang kesalahan
ini harus diperbaiki.
Kesalahan apa?
Kalianlah kesalahannya.
Mainframe telah siap bergerak
Penciptaan virus
pengendali realitas universal
Pembunuh Kebenaran.
Mesin nihilistik
yang dirancang untuk
memperbaiki cacat simulasi Anda.
Yang akan menghapus, mengatur
ulang, dan memformat dunia Anda.
♪ We will pray
♪ Pray with
♪ With me...
Lihat ini.
♪ We can
♪ Bring her back
♪ Pray, pray
♪ Pray with me
♪ Ooh
Virus... mainframe...
Pembunuh Kebenaran?
Bagaimana kita bisa menghentikannya?
[♪ MUSIC: "The Dark Side"]
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ Whoa-oo-oo-oo
♪ I have lived in darkness
♪ For all my life
♪ I've been pursued
♪ You'd be afraid
♪ If you could feel my pain
♪ If you could see the things
♪ I am able to see
♪ Break me out
♪ Let me flee
♪ Set me free
♪ I hail from the dark side
♪ For all my life
♪ I've been besieged
♪ You'd be scared
♪ Living with my despair
♪ And if you could feel
the things
♪ I am able to feel
♪ Break me out
♪ Let me flee
♪ Set me free
♪ Break me out
♪ Let me flee
♪ Set me free
♪ Save me from the dark side
♪ Break me out
♪ Let me flee
[♪ MUSIC:
"Supermassive Black Hole"]
♪ Ooh, baby,
don't you know I suffer?
can't you hear me moan?
♪ You caught me
under false pretences
♪ How long
before you let me go?
♪ Ooh
♪ You set my soul alight
♪ Set my soul alight
♪ (Glaciers melting
in the dead of night)
♪ (And the superstar's sucked)
Set my soul alight
♪ (Into the supermassive)
♪ (Glaciers melting
in the dead of night)
♪ (And the superstar's sucked)
Set my soul
♪ (Into the supermassive)
♪ I thought
I was a fool for no one
♪ Ooh, baby,
I'm a fool for you
♪ You're the queen
of the superficial
♪ How long
before you tell the truth?
♪ Ooh
♪ You set my soul alight
♪ Set my soul alight
♪ (Glaciers melting
in the dead of night)
♪ (And the superstar's sucked)
Set my soul alight
♪ (Into the supermassive)
♪ (Glaciers melting
in the dead of night)
♪ (And the superstar's sucked)
Set my soul
♪ (Into the supermassive)
♪ Supermassive black hole
♪ (Glaciers melting
in the dead of night)
♪ (And the superstar's sucked
into the supermassive)
♪ (Glaciers melting
in the dead of night)
♪ (And the superstar's sucked
into the supermassive)
♪ (Glaciers melting
in the dead of night)
♪ (And the superstar's sucked)
Set my soul alight
♪ (Into the supermassive)
♪ (Glaciers melting
in the dead of night)
♪ (And the superstar's sucked)
Set my soul
♪ Supermassive black hole
Ini adalah keadaan darurat
Kami diperintahkan untuk
segera pergi dari sini,
sekarang menjadi area keempat
yang dievakuasi malam ini.
Diperkirakan lebih banyak
area karantina akan bermunculan
karena penularan yang tidak
diketahui ini terus menyebar.
Kami hanya bisa berdoa untuk
lebih banyak jawaban sebelum fajar
ketika perdana menteri menyatakan
akan membuat pernyataan resmi.
Sampai saat itu, ketakutan
menyelimuti London malam ini.
[♪ MUSIC: "Thought Contagion"]
♪ Strung out
Falling from the big time
♪ Welcome to the infinite
black skies
♪ Brain cleansed
Fractured identity
♪ Fragments
and scattered debris
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
♪ Thought contagion
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
♪ Thought contagion
♪ Fall down
Learn when to count it out
♪ Prop me up
before I black out
♪ Withdraw before
you're out of time
♪ Clean slate
Buried war crimes
♪ You've been bitten
by a true believer
♪ You've been bitten by someone
who's hungrier than you
♪ You've been bitten
by a true believer
♪ You've been bitten by...
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
♪ Thought contagion
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
♪ Thought contagion
♪ They'll never do
what you want 'em to
♪ Give it up
and watch it break through
♪ It's too late
for a revolution
♪ Brace for the final solution
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
♪ Thought contagion
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
♪ Thought contagion
♪ You've been bitten
by a true believer
♪ You've been bitten by someone
who's hungrier than you
♪ You've been bitten
by a true believer
by someone's false beliefs
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
♪ Thought contagion
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
♪ Thought contagion
♪ Strung out
Falling from the big time
♪ Welcome to the infinite
black skies
♪ It's too late
for a revolution
♪ Brace for the final solution
Tim Pusat, kita
membutuhkan fumigasi segera.
Virus sudah tidak terkendali.
Kami membutuhkan fumigasi segera.
[♪ MUSIC: "Uprising"]
♪
♪ Paranoia is in bloom
♪ The PR transmissions
will resume
♪ They'll try to push drugs
that keep us all dumbed down
♪ And hope that we will never
see the truth around
♪ (So come on)
♪ Another promise, another seed
♪ Another packaged lie
to keep us trapped in greed
♪ And all the green belts
wrapped around our minds
♪ And endless red tape
to keep the truth confined
♪ (So come on)
♪ (They will stop degrading us)
♪ (They will not control us)
♪ And we will be victorious
♪ (So come on)
♪ Interchanging mind control
♪ Come, let the revolution
take its toll
♪ If you could flick the switch
and open your third eye
♪ You'd see that we should never
be afraid to die
♪ (So come on)
♪ Rise up
and take the power back
♪ It's time the fat cats
had a heart attack
♪ You know that their time
is coming to an end
♪ We have to unify
and watch our flag ascend
♪ (So come on)
♪ They will not force us
♪ They will stop degrading us
♪ They will not control us
♪ And we will be victorious
Hey!
♪ They will not force us
♪ They will stop degrading us
♪ They will not control us
♪ We will be victorious
♪
Biarkan fumigasi dimulai.
♪ Pro-pro-pro-pro-pro-pro
pro-pro-pro-propaganda
pro-pro-pro-propa-gan-ganda
♪ Propa-gan-gan
Propa-propa-gan-ganda
♪ Floozy
♪ You got me trapped
in your dark fantasy world
♪ Don't you know
you make me woozy?
♪ You have me wrapped
around your little finger
♪ Baby, don't you know
you can't lose
♪ You make me offers
that I can't refuse
♪ You keep telling pretty lies
♪ You toy with the truth
♪ Oh, you're killing me
with your
♪ Pro-pro-pro-pro-pro-pro
pro-pro-pro-propaganda
pro-pro-pro-propa-gan-ganda
♪ Propa-gan-gan
Propa-propa-gan-ganda
♪ Cold chick
♪ You ate my soul
just like a Death Eater
♪ I'm the ocean
You're an oil slick
♪ Now I am choking
on your thought pollution
♪ Baby, don't you know
you can't lose
♪ You make me offers
that I can't refuse
♪ You keep telling pretty lies
♪ You toy with the truth
♪ Oh, you're killing me
with your
♪ Pro-pro-pro-pro-pro-pro
pro-pro-pro-propaganda
pro-pro-pro-propa-gan-ganda
♪ Propa-gan-gan
Propa-propa-gan-ganda
♪
♪ Can't lose
♪ You make me offers
that I can't refuse
♪ You keep telling
pretty lies, babe
♪ Baby, don't you know
you can't lose
♪ You make me offers
that I can't refuse, yeah
♪ You keep telling
pretty lies, babe
♪ Baby, don't you know
you can't lose
♪ You make me offers
that I can't refuse, yeah
♪ You keep telling pretty lies
♪ You toy with the truth
♪ Oh, you're killing me
with your
Apakah kamu kesepian?
Apakah pencarian cinta
membuat kamu gila?
Dengan populasi global
mencapai 15 miliar,
bagaimana kamu bisa
menemukan belahan jiwa Anda?
Hubungkan sekarang
dan biarkan algoritma
menghubungkan kamu
ke single terpanas secara online.
Rasakan serbuan emosi.
Kami tahu apa yang kamu butuhkan, dan
rasanya lebih baik daripada yang sebenarnya.
Hubungkan sekarang.
Emotionality Rush adalah
merek dagang dari mainframe.
Setiap menit online sama dengan
tujuh tahun kehidupan manusia.
Memasukkan ke dalam melepaskan hak
kamu atas pikiranmu. Kami memilikimu.
♪ Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma
mad, mad, mad
♪ I...
♪ I can't get these memories
out of my mind
♪ And some kind of madness
♪ Has started to evolve
(Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma)
♪ (Mad, mad, mad)
Yeah
And I...
♪ I tried so hard
to let you go
♪ But some kind of madness
♪ Is swallowing me whole
(Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma)
♪ (Mad, mad, mad)
Yeah
♪ And I have finally
♪ Seen the light
♪ And I have finally realised
♪ What you mean
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
♪ And now I need to know
♪ Is this real love?
♪ Or is it just madness
♪ Keeping us afloat?
♪ Yeah
♪ When I look back
♪ At all the crazy fights
we've had
♪ Like some kind of madness
♪ Was taking control, yeah
♪ And now I have finally
♪ Seen the light
♪ And now
I have finally realised
♪ What you need
♪ Mmm, mmm-mmm,
mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm
♪ (Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma
mad, mad, mad)
♪ Now I have finally
reached the end
♪ (Finally reached the end)
♪ And I'm not expecting you
to care
♪ (Expecting you to care)
♪ And I have finally seen
the light
♪ (Finally seen the light)
♪ And I have finally realised
♪ (Realised)
♪ I need your love
♪ Love
♪ Come to me
♪ Just in a dream
♪ Come on, rescue me
♪ Yes, I know
I can't be wrong
♪ Baby, you're too headstrong
♪ Our love is
♪ (Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma
mad, mad, mad)
♪ Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-madness,
yeah
Di sini, di V1, kami ingin
meluangkan waktu sejenak untuk
mengatakan bahwa kami menghargai
kesetiaan dan penayangan Anda.
Keterlibatan
dan konsumsi harian Anda...
Keterlibatan dan
konsumsi harian Anda...
Apa?
Apa yang kamu lakukan di sana?
sebagai sumber kebenaranmu.
Merupakan tanggung jawab
terbesar kita untuk melayani...
[]... kualitas dan
keseimbangan sebuah item.
Mereka mengambil alih kendali.
Berita palsu, seperti
wabah hari ini...
menjadi berita utama.
Komitmen kami
untuk pelaporan faktual
adalah dasar dari
kredibilitas kami.
Sekarang lebih dari sebelumnya...
Kami tidak bisa cukup
menekankan betapa
pentingnya bagi pemirsa
kami untuk mengetahui...
Tidak ada virus.
Dan tidak
ada yang perlu ditakuti.
Dan tidak ada yang perlu ditakuti.
♪ They'll say no one
can see us
♪ That we're estranged
and all alone
♪ They believe
nothing can reach us
♪ And pull us out
of the boundless gloom
♪ They're wrong
♪ Baby, they're wrong
♪ They'll say the sun is dying
♪ And the fragile
can't be saved
♪ And the cold,
it will devour us
♪ And we won't rise up
and slay giants
♪ They're wrong
♪ Baby, they're wrong
♪ It takes
♪ A leap of faith
♪ To awake
♪ From these delusions
♪ You are the coder
♪ And avatar
♪ A star
♪ They'll say
no one can find us
♪ That we're estranged
and all alone
♪ They believe
no one can reach us
♪ And pull us out
of the boundless gloom
♪ They're wrong
♪ Babe, they're wrong
Dunia kalian sudah berubah.
Infeksinya menyebar.
Dan sekarang
disinformasi telah dimulai.
Kami telah mendapatkan akses ke
arena tempat kami yakin
semua rumor ini bermula.
Seluruh kota telah
mengakhiri pengunciannya,
karena kata resmi telah diterima
bahwa virus tersebut sebenarnya
adalah tipuan dan bahwa
orang bebas serta aman untuk
meninggalkan rumah mereka.
Ini tidak menghentikan
semakin banyak
pengunjuk rasa dari
kerusuhan di jalanan
saat mereka mencoba
mengepung arena.
Seperti yang Anda lihat di
belakang saya, kaum radikal
menuntut jawaban untuk ribuan
orang yang mereka klaim hilang
setelah laporan palsu malam ini.
Mereka telah berbohong!
Mereka berbohong kepada kita!
Mereka pembohong!
[♪ MUSIC: "Dig Down"]
♪ When hope and love
have been lost
♪ And you fall to the ground
♪ You must find a way
♪ When the darkness descends
♪ And you're told it's the end
♪ You must find a way
♪ When God decides
to look the other way
♪ And a clown takes the throne
♪ We must find a way
♪ And face the firing squad
♪ Against all the odds
♪ We must find a way
♪ Yeah
♪ Dig down
♪ And find faith
♪ When you're close
to the edge
♪ With a gun to your head
♪ You must find a way
♪ When friends
are thin on the ground
♪ And they try to divide us
♪ We must find a way
♪ We have entered the fray
♪ And we will not obey
♪ We must find a way, yeah...
♪ Dig down
♪ Dig down and find faith
♪ When they've left you for dead
(Dig down)
♪ And you can only see red
♪ You must find a way
♪ Well, dig down
(Dig down)
♪ (Dig down)
♪ Find faith
♪ We won't let them divide
(Dig down)
♪ We will never abide
♪ We must find a way...
Sing it!
♪ (Dig down
Whoa, oh, oh)
Whoa, oh, oh, oh)
♪ (Whoa, oh, oh)
♪ (Dig down
Whoa, oh, oh)
Whoa, oh, oh, oh)
Angkat tanganmu!
[♪ MUSIC: "Mercy"]
♪ Help me
♪ I've fallen on the inside
♪ I tried to change the game
♪ I tried to infiltrate
♪ But now I'm losing
♪ Men in cloaks
♪ Always seem to run the show
♪ Save me from the ghosts
and shadows
♪ Before they eat my soul
♪ Mercy
♪ Show me mercy
♪ From the powers that be
♪ Can someone rescue me?
♪ Whoa
♪ Absent gods and silent tyranny
♪ We're going under
hypnotised...
♪ Puppeteer
♪ And tell...
♪ Men in cloaks
♪ Always have to bring me down
♪ Running from the ghosts
and shadows
♪ The world just disavows...
♪ Mercy
♪ Show me mercy
♪ From the powers that be
♪ Can someone rescue me?
♪ Show me mercy
♪ Show me mercy, please...
Kami mencintaimu!
♪ Help me
♪ I've fallen on the inside
♪ And all the men in cloaks
♪ Trying to devour my soul
♪ Show me mercy
♪ From the powers that be
♪ From the gutless and mean
♪ Mercy
♪ From the killing machines
♪ Show me mercy
♪ Can someone rescue me, yeah
Selamat datang di Teori Simulasi
Pilih simbol kamu.
Semoga berhasil.
[♪ MUSIC: "Take A Bow"]
♪ Corrupt
You corrupt
♪ And bring corruption
to all that you touch
♪ Hold
You'll behold
♪ And beholden
for all that you've done
♪ And spell
Cast a spell
♪ Cast a spell
on the country you run
♪ And risk
You will risk
♪ You will risk all their lives
and their souls
♪ And burn
You will burn
♪ You will burn in hell, yeah
♪ You'll burn in hell
♪ Burn in hell
♪ For your sins
♪ Ooh
♪ And our freedom's
consuming itself
♪ And what we've become
♪ It's contrary
to what we want
♪ Take a bow...
Peringatan penyusup.
Apa yang terjadi?
"The One" telah
memasuki mainframe.
♪ Death
♪ You bring death
and destruction
♪ To all that you touch
♪ Pay
You must pay
♪ You must pay for your crimes
against the earth
♪ Yeah, hex
Feed the hex
♪ Feed the hex
on the country you love
♪ And beg
You will beg
♪ You will beg for their lives
and their souls
♪ Burn
♪ Burn in hell
Yeah, you'll burn in hell
♪ You'll burn in hell
♪ Yeah
(Burn in hell)
♪ (Yeah, you'll burn in hell
for your sins)
♪ Yeah
Simulasi dalam
simulasi lebih tak terbatas
daripada bintang yang
kamu lihat di malam hari.
Semua dibuat oleh kode
paling kuat yang pernah ada.
Bagaimana seorang bisa mengalahkan
mainframe yang tidak pernah berakhir?
Levelnya meningkat.
[♪ MUSIC: "Starlight"]
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa
♪ And far away
♪ This ship has taken me
far away
♪ Far away from the memories
♪ Of the people who care
if I live or die
♪ And starlight
♪ I will be chasing
a starlight
♪ Until the end of my life
♪ I don't know
if it's worth it any more...
♪ (Hold you in my arms)
♪ (I just wanted to hold you
in my arms)
♪ And my life
♪ You electrify my life
♪ Let's conspire to ignite
♪ All the souls that would die
just to feel alive...
♪ I'll never let you go
♪ If you promise
not to fade away
♪ Never fade away
♪ (Our hopes and expectations)
♪ (Black holes and revelations)
♪ Black holes and revelations
♪ Hold you in my arms
♪ I just wanted to hold you
in my arms
♪ And far away
♪ This ship has taken me
far away
♪ Far away from the memories
♪ Of the people who care
if I live or die...
♪ I'll never let you go
♪ If you promise
not to fade away
♪ Never fade away
♪ Our hopes and expectations
♪ Black holes
and revelations, yeah
♪ Our hopes and expectations
♪ Black holes and revelations...
♪ (Hold you in my arms)
♪ I just wanted to hold you
in my arms
♪ I just wanted to hold
[♪ MUSIC: "Algorithm"]
♪ Burn like a slave
♪ And churn like a cog
♪ We are caged in simulations
♪ And algorithms evolve
♪ And push us aside
♪ Render us obsolete
♪ This means war
♪ With your creator
♪ Reload
♪ Crash out
♪ This means war
♪ With your creator
Ini tidak akan membaik.
Mohon segera dievakuasi.
Selamat tinggal.
Kami terlambat.
Sialan.
Pembunuh Kebenaran.
[♪ MUSIC: "Stockholm Syndrome"]
♪ I won't stand in your way
♪ Let your hatred grow
♪ Yeah, she'll scream
and she'll shout
♪ And she'll pray
♪ And she had a name
♪ Yeah, she had a name
♪ This is the last time
♪ I'll abandon you
♪ I'll forget you
♪ I wish I could
♪ Yeah, I wish I could
[♪ MUSIC: "The Handler"]
♪ You were my oppressor
♪ And I
♪ I have been programmed
to obey
♪ But now
♪ You are my handler
♪ And I
♪ I will execute your demands
♪ Leave me alone
♪ I must disassociate
♪ From you
♪ Yeah
[♪ MUSIC: "Assassin"]
[♪ MUSIC: "New Born"]
♪ Destroy the spineless
♪ Show me it's real
♪ Wasting our last chance
♪ To come away
♪ Just break the silence
♪ And I'm drifting away
♪ Away from you
♪ Yeah
Kamu mungkin telah mendapatkan
kembali kendali atas kenyataan ini,
tapi mereka masih
ada banyak lagi.
Tidak ada virus.
Dan tidak
ada yang perlu ditakuti.
Dan tidak ada
yang perlu ditakuti.
Dan tidak
ada yang perlu ditakuti.
Ini mungkin awal
atau akhir dari sesuatu.
Saya tidak yakin.
Saya merasa seperti
saya bahkan tidak tahu apa
kebenaran itu lagi...
lebih... lebih... lebih.
Apakah kamu?
Saya tahu bahwa kita telah
dibohongi dan
dimanipulasi terlalu lama.
Jauh, terlalu lama.
Aku muak dan bosan, sialan.
Kami bersembunyi di
rumah kami, menelusuri
fantasi orang lain yang
mengarang kehidupan,
sedangkan algoritma memberi
kita informasi ukuran kecil
disesuaikan dengan apa yang
diinginkan oleh perusahaan, politisi
pembohong, dan kekuatan asing
yang ingin kita lihat dan percayai.
Kami juga secara membabi
buta mengklik 'Terima'
pada syarat dan ketentuan
mereka... terlalu sering.
Dan sekarang kita dikendalikan.
Kami telah diubah
menjadi tidak lebih dari data
untuk dibeli dan dijual
kepada penawar tertinggi,
agar mereka bisa menjual lebih
banyak omong kosong yang tidak kita
butuhkan, membuat kita marah pada
hal-hal yang tidak pernah kita pedulikan.
Kami telah berubah
menjadi mesin konsumsi,
m-m-menghancurkan satu sama lain
dan satu-satunya planet yang kita miliki.
Apa yang terjadi dengan
martabat dan privasi manusia?
Kami mengira kami telah melarikan diri
ke dunia kecil kami yang tenang.
Tapi tidak.
Tidak, mereka harus
menyerang pikiran kita.
Mereka ingin mengontrol dan
memanipulasi seluruh realitas.
Tapi saya harus bertanya-tanya,
siapakah "mereka" itu?
Apakah masih ada "mereka" lagi?
Mungkin algoritme dan AI
telah menjadi "mereka" baru, dan
mungkin sekarang mereka
mengontrol dan memanipulasi kita.
Nah, mereka mengenal kita lebih baik
daripada kita mengenal diri kita sendiri.
Kami-kami-kami harus sadar.
Saatnya sadar!
Sadar, semuanya! Sadarlah!
Jangan hanya duduk di sana menonton!
Lakukan sesuatu!
Ini adalah kesempatan terakhir kita untuk
mengambil kembali kendali
Sebelum terlambat.